<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="error_unknown">A surprising error has occurred. Try again.</string>
  <string name="error_canceled">Action has been canceled</string>
  <string name="error_network_connection">Please check the network connection</string>

  <string name="error_incomplete_info_message">Try again in a moment</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_achievements">There was an error when fetching the list of achievements</string>
  <string name="error_empty_achievement_list">Sorry, there are no achievements for now.</string>

  <string name="error_alert_insufficient_info">There is insufficient information to submit the alert</string>
  <string name="error_alert_target_price_invalid">Target price cannot be zero.</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_exchange_list_info">There was an error when fetching the list of exchanges</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_help_video_list_info">There was an error when fetching the list of help videos</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_hero">There was an error when fetching the hero information</string>


  <string name="error_fetch_leaderboard_def_list_key">There was an error when fetching the definition list of leaderboards</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_leaderboard_info">There was an error when fetching the current leaderboard information</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_message_thread_header">Failed to fetch the message thread info</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_portfolio_list_info">There was an error when fetching the list of portfolios</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_portfolio_info">There was an error when fetching the portfolio information</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_provider_info_list">There was an error when fetching the list of competition providers.</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_provider_info">There was an error when fetching the competition provider info.</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_provider_competition_list">There was an error when fetching the list of competitions</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_provider_competition_display_cell_list">There was an error when fetching the list of competition\'s items</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_security_list_info">There was an error when fetching the list of securities</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_security_info">There was an error when fetching the security information</string>

  <string name="error_decode_image_memory">Not enough memory to decode the image</string>
  <string name="error_launch_photo_library">There was an error launching the photo library</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_user_profile">There was an error when fetching the user profile information</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_your_user_profile">There was an error when fetching your profile information</string>
  <string name="error_update_your_user_profile">There was an error when updating your profile information</string>
  <string name="error_fetch_people_list_info">There was an error when fetching the list of people</string>
  <string name="error_save_image_in_external_storage">Error in saving image in external storage of your device.</string>

  <string name="error_fetch_portfolio_watchlist">There was an error when fetching the watch list</string>
  <string name="error_no_internet_connection">Cannot connect to server, please check your internet connection.</string>

</resources>